[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the correct order of the years of release of the Alien movies?", "correct_answer": "1979, 1986, 1992, 1997, 2004", "incorrect_answers": ["1978, 1986, 1995, 1997, 2004", "1978, 1984, 1991, 1996, 2003", "1977, 1986, 1993, 1997, 2002"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I think we have all heard this one. Does an apple a day keep the doctor away?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Roman god of war Mars corresponds to which god from the Greek mythology?", "correct_answer": "Ares", "incorrect_answers": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Hermes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Rifleman was one of the TV westerns Johnny Crawford starred in.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year marked the first broadcast of a baseball game?", "correct_answer": "1939", "incorrect_answers": ["1949", "1946", "1929"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cancerophobia is a condition characterized by fear of malignant growth.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film My Girl, what did Vada swear was stuck in her throat?", "correct_answer": "chicken bone", "incorrect_answers": ["chewing gum", "lemon seed", "corn cobb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Polar bears possess extremely good eyesight, compared to most land animal species.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Do you like listening to MP3s? What does this mystical acronym mean?", "correct_answer": "Moving Picture Experts Group Layer-3 Audio", "incorrect_answers": ["Most Popular Layer-3 Audio", "Movable Protocol for Layer-3 Audio", "Modern Protocol 3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who won the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor for his outstanding performance in a 1997 movie?", "correct_answer": "Kevin Costner in The Postman", "incorrect_answers": ["Val Kilmer in The Saint", "Jon Voight in Anaconda", "Steven Seagal in Fire Down Below"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Appaloosa Jeremy Irons plays Randall Bragg, who claims to have a connection with a U.S. President.  Which president does he claim to know?", "correct_answer": "Chester A. Arthur", "incorrect_answers": ["Ulysses S. Grant", "James A. Garfield", "Teddy Roosevelt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Persian Empire was divided into 20 provinces, each called this.", "correct_answer": "Satrapy", "incorrect_answers": ["Larsa", "Uruk", "Assur"]}]